Mahmoud Al Masri Al Shayyah

Saida, South, Lebanon

Mahmoud.Masri1996@gmail.com



+961 70/293986



linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-al-masri-al-shayyah



https://github.com/Mahmoud-ms1996

Summary

Hi, I'm Mahmoud Al Masri Al Shayyah. Junior Front-End Developer with 1 year of experience designing and building responsive web design in the Freelancers. Proficient with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, swiper.js. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved Code and Design.

Experience



Training C# Developer

El Haceb

Dec 2021 - Jan 2022 (2 months)

Full-stack Developer

KE business Development consulting Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

Education

Lebanese International University Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Nov 2017 - Aug 2021 Web developer



Saida Technical Institute

Technical Baccalaureate - BT3, Industrial Mechanical 2015 - 2016

Licenses & Certifications



Front-End Web Development - Udemy

Skills

Front-End Development • Web Design • Research • User Experience Design (UED) • Web Services • Bootstrap • HTML5 • PHP • MySQL • Back-End Web Development